Finding aid to the Classes of 1931-1940 records CA.MS.01015
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1936 Records, 1932-2000; 1.875 linear feet (5 containers)
  The Class of 1936 was the fifty-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1936 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1936, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Dramatics, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Dramatics-Photographs, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1932-1933 (Box 2068, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1932-1936 (Box 2068, Folder 8)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 11)
  - Junior Prom, 1935 (Box 2068, Folder 12)
  - Junior Ushers, 1935 (Box 2068, Folder 13)
  - Last Chapel, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1956-2000 (Box 2068, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 2068, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 2068, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1946-1951 (Box 2068, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 2068, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1961-1966 (Box 2068, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1971-1976 (Box 2068, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1981 (Box 2068, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1986 (Box 2068, Folder 23)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 24)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2068, Folder 25)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1934 (Box 2068, Folder 26)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1934 (Box 2068, Folder 27)
  - Step Sings, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 28)
  - Class Supper, 1936 (Box 2068, Folder 29)
  - Individuals A-Z (Box 2069)
  - Campbell, Cloyce Cooley (memorabilia book from Junior Year Abroad in France) (Box 2070)
  - Grosberg, Marian (publications) (Box 2071)
  - Tyler, Ruth (Box 2072)
- Class of 1937 Records, 1933-2002; 8.792 linear feet (23 containers)
  The Class of 1937 was the fifty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1937 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1937, including materials from commencement activities, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, letters, financial records, and other memorabilia.
  - Clippings, 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Dramatics, 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 6)
  - First Chapel, 1933 (Box 2100, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1933-1934 (Box 2100, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1933-1937 (Box 2100, Folder 9)
  - Smith Girl's Guide Book, 1936-1937 (Box 2100, Folder 10)
  - History, 1933-1937 (Box 2100, Folder 11)
  - History, 1972 (Box 2100, Folder 12)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day, 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 1)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 2)
  - Junior Prom, 1936 (Box 2101, Folder 3)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1936 (Box 2101, Folder 4)
  - Junior Ushers, 1936 (Box 2101, Folder 5)
  - Last Chapel, 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 6)
  - Class Letters, 1956-2002 (Box 2101, Folder 7)
  - Class Officers, 1934 (Box 2101, Folder 8)
  - Organization, 1933 (Box 2101, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1938 (Box 2101, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 2101, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 2101, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 2101, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 2101, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 2101, Folder 15)
  - Reunions-"A Myoptic Report", 1957 (Box 2101, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 2101, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 2101, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 2101, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1977-1982 (Box 2101, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1987-1992 (Box 2101, Folder 21)
  - Reunion, 1997 (Box 2101.1)
  - Reunion Memoribilia, 2018-A-0045; 1 items (1 videotape) (Box 2108.3)
    Videotapes
  - Reunions-Songs, 1972-1987 (Box 2101.1, Folder 22)
  - Class Scrapbook (Box 2108.2)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1937 (Box 2101.1, Folder 23)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2101.1, Folder 24)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1935 (Box 2101.1, Folder 25)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1935 (Box 2101.1, Folder 26)
  - Step Sings, 1937 (Box 2101.1, Folder 27)
  - Class Supper, 1937 (Box 2101.1, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer, 1933-1937 (Box 2101.1, Folder 29)
  - Year Book, 1936-1937 (Box 2101.1, Folder 30)
  - Individuals A-O (Box 2102)
  - Individuals P-Z (Box 2102.1)
  - Barry, Barbara Reed (class notes, correspondence) (Box 2103)
  - Chafee, Dorothy Wilson (scrapbook), 1933-1972 (Box 2108.1)
  - Davenport, Deborah Lois (class notes, etc.) (Box 2104)
  - Goddard, Margaret (papers, Junior Year Abroad in France) (Box 2106)
  - Marr, Mary (photo album, class notes, general) (Box 2106.1)
  - Myers, Margaret (Transcripts) (Box 2106.2)
  - Myers, Margaret (Correspondence) (Box 2106.3)
  - Myers, Margaret (Correspondence) (Box 2106.4)
  - Myers, Margaret (Correspondence) (Box 2106.5)
  - Myers, Margaret (Correspondence) (Box 2106.6)
  - Myers, Margaret (Correspondence) (Box 2106.7)
  - Myers, Margaret (Correspondence) (Box 2106.8)
  - Myers, Margaret (Correspondence) (Box 2106.9)
  - Myers, Margaret (Miscellaneous and Photographs) (Box 2106.10)
  - Pfening, Katherine Wells (papers, college years) (Box 2107)
  - Wriggins, Helen Virginia (papers, college years) (Box 2108)
- Class of 1938 Records, 1934-2004; 9.958 linear feet (17 containers)
  The Class of 1938 was the sixtieth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1938 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1938, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Dramatics, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Dramatics-Photographs, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1934-1935 (Box 2109, Folder 8)
  - Fund Letters, 1988-1991 (Box 2109, Folder 9)
  - Smith Girls' Guidebook, 1937-38 (Box 2109, Folder 9a)
  - Groups, 1934-1938 (Box 2109, Folder 10)
  - History, 1937; undated (Box 2109, Folder 11)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 14)
  - Junior Prom, 1937 (Box 2109, Folder 15)
  - Junior Ushers, 1937 (Box 2109, Folder 16)
  - Last Chapel, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1957-2004 (Box 2109, Folder 18)
  - Class Officers, 1935-1938; 1958 (Box 2109, Folder 19)
  - Class Officers' Meetings-Minutes, 1979-1993 (Box 2109, Folder 20)
  - Rally Day, 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1953 (Box 2109, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 2109, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 2109, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 2109, Folder 25)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 2109.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1983 (Box 2109.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1988 (Box 2109.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1993 (Box 2109.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunion photo albums, 1958-1993; 2018-A-0046; Smith College--Alumnae Association; 6 items (6 photo albums in four different flat boxes) (Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
    6 photo albums from the 1958, 1963, 1968, 1973, 1978, 1983, 1988, and 1993 reunions
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred from the Smith College Alumnae Association
    photograph albums; Smith College--Alumnae Association
  - Reunion scrapbook, 1978-1983 (Box 2109.2)
  - Scrapbook, 1948-1953 (Box 2109.3)
  - Scrapbook, 1958-1963 (Box 2109.4)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 5)
  - Senior Prom, 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 6)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 7)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2109.1, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1936 (Box 2109.1, Folder 9)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1936 (Box 2109.1, Folder 10)
  - Step Sings, 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 11)
  - Class Supper, 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 12)
  - Year Book, 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 13)
  - Individuals A-Ch (Box 2110)
  - Individuals Co-O (Box 2111)
  - Individuals P-Z (Box 2111.1)
  - Capen, Jane (Photo album), 1934-1941; Accession 2018-A-0046; Capen, Jane, Class of 1938; Smith College--Alumnae Association; 1 items (1 photo album in a flat box, with the scrapbook of Sarah Wallis, Class of 1938) (Box 1)
    Photo album of Jane Capen, Class of 1938, containing photographs of her family, years at Smith, and travels after college.
    Transferred by the Smith College Alumnae Association.
  - Eustice, Helen (book "Holiday May 1950") (Box 1683.1)
  - Hamilton, Agnes Black (scrapbook) (Box 2111.3)
  - Heffernan, Helen Frances (scrapbook) (Box 2111.4)
  - High, Natalie (Photographs) (Box 2111.2)
  - Wallis, Sarah (Sas) Stevens (Scrapbook), 1934-1938; 2018-A-0046; Smith College--Alumnae Association; Sarah (Sas) Wallis Stevens, Class of 1938; 1 items (1 scrapbook in a flat box with the scrapbook of Jane Capen, Class of 1938) (Box 1)
    The personal scrapbook of Sarah (Sas) Wallis Stevens, Class of 1938, containing photographs and clippings from her years at Smith.
    Transferred from the Alumnae Association.
    scrapbooks; Smith College--Alumnae Association
- Class of 1939 Records, 1935-2004; 7.667 linear feet (12 containers)
  The Class of 1939 was the sixty-first graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1939 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1939, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Dramatics, 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1935-1936 (Box 2112, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1935-1939 (Box 2112, Folder 6)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 1)
  - Ivy Day-Music, 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 2)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 3)
  - Junior Prom, 1938 (Box 2113, Folder 4)
  - Junior Ushers, 1938 (Box 2113, Folder 5)
  - Last Chapel, 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 6)
  - Class Letters, 1956-2001 (Box 2113, Folder 7)
  - Officers, 1935-1939; 1957 (Box 2113, Folder 8)
  - Rally Day, 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 2113, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1945 (Box 2113, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 2113, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 2113, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 2113, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 2113, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 2113, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 2113, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 2113, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1984 (Box 2113, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2113.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2113.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2113.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2113.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1999 (Box 2113.1, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 2004 (Box 2113.1, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 7)
  - Senior Prom, 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 8)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2113.1, Folder 9)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1937 (Box 2113.1, Folder 10)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1937 (Box 2113.1, Folder 11)
  - Step Sings, 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 12)
  - Class Supper, 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 13)
  - Year Book, 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 14)
  - Individuals A-Z (Box 2114)
  - Allen, Martha Browne (correspondence) (Box 2115)
  - Coulter, Helen (scrapbook) (Box 2118.1)
  - Coulter, Helen (scrapbook) (Box 2118.2)
  - Daniels, Eleanor (Box 2116)
  - Middaugh, Anna Zakel (scrapbook) (Box 2118.3)
  - Middaugh, Anna Zakel (scrapbook) (Box 2118.4)
  - Shedd, Kathleen (Box 2117)
  - Walsh, Cynthia Stanton (Box 2118)
- Class of 1940 Records, 1936-2002; 4.437 linear feet (10 containers)
  The Class of 1940 was the sixty-second graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1940 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1940, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
  - Class Animal, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Music, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 4)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 5)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1936-1937 (Box 2119, Folder 8)
  - Class Gift to Mrs. Morrow, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 9)
  - Groups, 1936-1940 (Box 2119, Folder 10)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1939 (Box 2119, Folder 14)
  - Junior Ushers, 1939 (Box 2119, Folder 15)
  - Last Chapel, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 16)
  - Last Sing, 1940 (Box 2119, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1955-2002 (Box 2119, Folder 18)
  - Mademoiselle Magazine Questionnaire, 1950 (Box 2120, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1936-1940; undated (Box 2119, Folder 19)
  - Officers, 1936-1940 (Box 2120, Folder 2)
  - Photo album and memoribilia (Box 2122.1)
  - Photographs, 1936 (Box 2120, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 2120, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1945 (Box 2120, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1950 (Box 2120, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 2120, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 2120, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 2120, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 2120, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 2120, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1980 (Box 2120, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1985 (Box 2120, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1990 (Box 2120, Folder 14)
  - 50th Reunion photo album and book (Box 2122)
  - Reunions, 1995 (Box 2120, Folder 15)
  - Secretary's Records (Correspondence), 1956-1990 (Box 2119, Folder 20)
  - Secretary's Records (Financial Information), 1957-1988 (Box 2119, Folder 21)
  - Secretary's Records (Information for Class Secretaries), 1980; 1990; undated (Box 2119, Folder 22)
  - Secretary's Records (Minutes of Class Officer's Meetings), 1960; 1965-1970; 1988 (Box 2119, Folder 23)
  - Secretary's Records (Class News Cards), 1955-1970 (Box 2119, Folder 24)
  - Secretary's Records (Class Newsletters), 1957-1990 (Box 2119, Folder 25)
  - Secretary's Records (Reports for Class Meetings), 1955-1990 (Box 2119, Folder 26)
  - Secretary's Records (Reunions), 1965-1975 (Box 2119, Folder 27)
  - Secretary's Class File (Box 2124.4)
  - Senior Dinner Dance, 1940 (Box 2120, Folder 16)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1940 (Box 2120, Folder 17)
  - Senior Prom, 1940 (Box 2120, Folder 18)
  - Senior Statistics, 1940 (Box 2120, Folder 19)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2120, Folder 20)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1938 (Box 2120, Folder 21)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1938 (Box 2120, Folder 22)
  - Step Sings, 1940 (Box 2120, Folder 23)
  - Class Supper, 1940 (Box 2120, Folder 24)
  - Year Book, 1940 (Box 2120, Folder 25)
  - Individuals A-Z (Box 2121)
  - Bowker, Nancy (class notes, papers) (Box 2123)
  - Carley, Margaret (class notes, papers) (Box 2124)
  - Carley, Margaret (scrapbook and photo album) (Box 2124.2)
  - Feick, Eleanor (photo album) (Box 2124.3)